Hey everyone, I want to talk to you about something extremely uncomfortable,
but it's important that we understand how the world works. I want to talk to you about
secret societies and with everything that's being uncovered by the Epstein files. It's clear that
there is a small elite group of people that share an ideology and a center of power in Israel that
are running our world. But why? The truth is this is how secret societies have worked, not just now,
but throughout history. Ritual is exactly how they yield so much power and are able to keep the
group closed, cohesive, and secret. And for those of you who follow Professor Zhang and his channel
Predictive History, this is exactly what he talks about. The three mechanics of secret societies.
The first mechanic, incentives. See, the higher you climb, the more incentives you get, the more power
you have. However, the higher you climb, the more secrets you are told. And the secrets get worse
and worse and worse the higher you climb. Therefore, keeping these secrets is exactly what keeps you
reaping the benefits of climbing up the ladder. That's why industries like the Hollywood industry,
like the music industry, are built upon such awful, disgusting secrets. Essentially, they're built upon
ritual human sacrifice. The second mechanism of secret societies is blackmail. See, if you really
want to climb to the very, very top, you have to commit crimes with each other. That way, you can never
betray each other. If I tell on you, you'll tell on me. However, even more than committing crimes,
you need to transgress the breaking of social norms, of social taboos. And there is the ultimate
transgression in society. See, once you perform this, and you're not held accountable, and you're
not punished, this group now feels like they have the ultimate power, like they can do anything. They
feel like they legitimately are God. And the third and last mechanism is something that I call deep
sleep. Because we don't want to believe that our government lies to us. We don't want to believe
that our favorite celebrity is compromised and depraved. We don't want to believe it. And so we don't.
And they do it in public, in front of everyone, underneath their noses. And the interesting
thing is the example that Professor Zhang was talking about when he was talking about
is that he wasn't talking about the Epstein revelations. He was talking about Israel. We were
all witness to the most public, depraved, televised, documented, photographed ritual
in the history of the world. And many of us did not do a thing about it. Because when
we say Free Palestine, we're not just talking about a plot of land. We are talking about humanity
itself.